http://www.dmcantor.com/privacy-policy

Contact Us
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which DM Cantor collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the dmcantor.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by DM Cantor.
Sharing your personal information / Targeted advertisements
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users Personal Identification Information (PII) to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any Personal Identification Information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined below.
Click Here to Opted Out of Targeted Advertising
Personal Identification Information
We may collect Personal Identification Information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect Personal Identification Information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply Personal Identification Information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-Personal Identification Information
We may collect Non-Personal Identification Information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-Personal Identification Information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
DM Cantor may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
– To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
– To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
– To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
– To show you our online ads
We may use your cookied browser to show you only our ads on websites with whom we partner and which you visit.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
DM Cantor has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
DM Cantor
dmcantor.com
40 N Central Ave. Ste 2300, Phoenix, AZ 85004
602-307-0808
info@dmcantor.com
This document was last updated on April 19, 2018
FREE INITIAL CONSULTATION
Your Name (required):
Your Phone (required):
Your Email (required):
Subject Matter (required):
---DUI/DWI/OUISex CrimeFraud/Theft CrimeAssault/Violent CrimeCrime Against PropertyDrug CrimePrecharge CasePost Conviction/AppealProbation ViolationForfeitureRelease/ExtraditionMisc Crime
Your Message (optional):
Results depend upon factors unique to each case and that results in one case do not predict similar results in others.
Request a Free Consultation
Fill out the form below to receive a free and confidential initial consultation.
Click here for important legal disclaimer.
-- Select Topic (required)DUI/DWI/OUISex CrimeFraud/Theft CrimeAssault/Violent CrimeCrime Against PropertyDrug CrimePrecharge CasePost Conviction/AppealProbation ViolationForfeitureRelease/ExtraditionMisc Crime
×
Notice
Communications through this website do not establish an attorney-client relationship. Any information sent to DM Cantor before establishing an attorney-client relationship will not be held in confidence, and may be used for the benefit of the firm's other clients or future clients. Accordingly, unless and until we formally establish an attorney-client relationship, do NOT send or otherwise communicate to us any information you would want to be maintained in confidence, whether through this website, through any email address posted on this website, or otherwise.
Close
CURRENT/PAST ASSOCIATIONS & AWARDS
10.0 Superb RatingAVVO Criminal Defense
AV-Highest Rated Preeminent LawyersMartindale-Hubbell
Life MemberNational Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers
Super LawyerCriminal & DUI Defense
MemberNational College for DUI Defense
Voted #1 (2020)Ranking Arizona
Top 1% AttorneyNational Association of Distinguished Counsel
Top 100 Trial Lawyers(Criminal Defense)American Trial Lawyers Association
Top 10 DUI/DWI Law FirmAmerican Institute of DUI / DWI Attorneys
Client Satisfaction AwardAmerican Institute of DUI / DWI Attorneys
2019 Litigator of the Year(Criminal Law)American Institute of Trial Lawyers
Member Since 1989American Bar Association
Best DUI Lawyers in PhoenixExpertise
Call 24/7 602-307-0808
40 N Central Ave, Ste 2300Phoenix, AZ 85004Click here for Directions
For Family Law questions please go to Cantor Law Group.
"We Outwork the Other Guys™"
